interlude.hk 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy : Interlude.hk

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy will explain how Interlude (“we”) uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.

**Topics:**

  * What data do we collect?
  * How do we collect your data?
  * How will we use your data?
  * How do we store your data?
  * Marketing
  * What are your data protection rights?
  * What are cookies?
  * How do we use cookies?
  * What types of cookies do we use?
  * How to manage your cookies
  * Privacy policies of other websites
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us
  * How to contact the appropriate authorities

## What data do we collect?

**We collect the following data:**

  * Personal identification information (Name and email address)

## How do we collect your data?

**You directly provide Interlude with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:**

  * Subscribe to our newsletter services.
  * Post comments on our website
  * Use or view our website via your browser’s cookies.

## How will we use your data?

**We collect your data so that we can:**

  * Email you with our regular newsletters 
  * Verify your comments on our website

## How do we store your data?

We securely store your data at our password protected database.

Our newsletter service is provided by Reasonable Software House Limited. Registered data is stored at their database. You have the right at any time to unsubscribe from the service.

## Marketing

We would like to send you information about our latest articles. You have the right at any time to stop Interlude from contacting you for marketing purposes.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#533a3d353c133a3d2736213f2637367d3b38).

## What are your data protection rights?

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

**The right to access**  – You have the right to request us for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

**The right to rectification**  – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the information you believe is incomplete.

**The right to erasure**  – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

**The right to restrict processing**  – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

**The right to object to processing**  – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

**The right to data portability**  – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#761f181019361f180213041a031213581e1d)

## Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology

For further information, visit [allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

## How do we use cookies?

**Interlude uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:**

  * Keeping you signed in
  * Understanding how you use our website

## What types of cookies do we use?

There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:

**Functionality** – Interlude uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.>

**Advertising** – Interlude uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. We sometimes share some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website.

## How to manage cookies

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

## Privacy policies of other websites

Interlude website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Interlude keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on July 2019.

## How to contact us

If you have any questions about Interlude’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Email us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9ff6f1f9f0dff6f1ebfaedf3eafbfab1f7f4)
